<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Book>
  <Chapter Id="e3ca5fa9-f99f-4ee8-bcb4-230d9bc7f4ce" Title="A Land Far From The Sun" Order="1">
    <Section Id="d7041816-e99b-4754-af35-c54a06f13a6c" Title="The Angry Father" DateCreated="9/10/2018 1:57:22 PM" LastUpdated="10/15/2018 9:04:41 PM"><![CDATA[<p>Razor ice crystals crooked at jutting angles in a defensive scowl.&nbsp;A howling wind whipped about angrily in no particular direction.&nbsp;Low on the horizon, a dim star offered only a puny amount of light and little else.&nbsp;Spiny thornned brambles frozen stiff.&nbsp;The vicious, ground strangling vines would gladly shred the old man’s feet to ribbons.&nbsp;Reluctantly the miniature crystal structures gave way, shattering to shrapnel as Rosbesh crunched through the harsh bitter world into which he was born so long ago.&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;No morning that gave way to evenings where this man trudged across the gray ice marsh.&nbsp;No margin for error, no opportunity to make a mistake more than once.&nbsp;To fail to prepare for one winter ensured it was your last.&nbsp;To lie down for a moment’s rest was to die.&nbsp;To mistake the useless sun as a reference was to be tricked into traveling into a circle, something that did not happen twice in this unforgiving land.&nbsp;A few dozen hours without shelter or sustenance meant only one thing here: Death.</p><p>&nbsp;Although formidable, Rosbesh was not the biggest of men.&nbsp;However, he had managed to live a long time, which itself was something.&nbsp;At almost forty years of age, he had already lived twice as long as most.&nbsp;His young wife waited for him in the cold and only put some more peat on the fire when he arrived.&nbsp;No reason to attract undue attention from the smoke when he wasn’t there anyway.&nbsp;Their two children huddled dopily, wrapped in skins on the straw. Rosbesh burst through the well sealed and highly camoflogued door and struggled to quickly re-close it as the blustering wind strove to evacuate all the warmth that had been sealed in his tiny dirt hovel.&nbsp;Karish, the wife smiled at him. Rosbesh merely inhaled through his nose freeing a mass of thawed phlegm which he expelled in a loud grunt onto the packed mud wall.&nbsp;He glanced over at his listless children, an older girl and a boy of eight or nine seasons, both with white blonde hair and cobalt blue eyes.&nbsp;They wrapped their knees protectively near their chins, and stared at him wide eyed, anxious to see what meat his traps might have yielded, but ever uncertain of their father’s mood.&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;Seeing them napping there like vegetables doing nothing more than taking up space seemed to anger him.&nbsp;Never mind that is was minus twenty degrees outside, and the wind was howling furiously.&nbsp;“Kids these days!” Rosbesh thought.&nbsp;“All they do is sit around and wait to be fed. Why don’t they ever get out and do something?&nbsp;Why in my day…”&nbsp;Karish picked up the sack her husband had dropped and greedily uncover the duck he had recovered from one of his traps.&nbsp;She began to titter and hum and set about preparing a meal.&nbsp;The children took brief interest but showed no signs of making any effort to help their mother.&nbsp;At this Rosbesh snarled.&nbsp;“Unappreciative!”&nbsp;How he hated sensing his best efforts go unappreciated.&nbsp;He picked up his stick and started a loathing vent.&nbsp;Then he started roaring in such a way as to make it clear that he wanted the children to go outside.</p><p>&nbsp;Their mother was horrified.&nbsp;Any threat to the safety of her babies elicited her most primal response, but fear of Rosbesh and her and her children’s utter dependence on him for their existance, prevailed.&nbsp;Plus, the kids had been kind of getting on her nerves too.&nbsp;Before they could even get themselves well bundled, Rosbesh made it clear that it would be prudent for them both to make use of the front door immediately.&nbsp;Swan, his daughter, revealed as she was roused from the warmth of the straw bed, that she was rapidly taking on the shape of woman and was already being visited on by the curse. Rosbesh noted this with unconcealed disgust.&nbsp;“What a waste, a female child!”&nbsp;Her legs were long and her arms seemed just as long.&nbsp;Like a gangly spider she sprawled and stumbled about, having been in no way prepared to be flushed from her cozy nest.</p><p>&nbsp;Out she and her brother stumbled, her arms raised high as she attempted to slip through a fur coat like wrap.&nbsp;The awkward pose exposed the full riches of her body as she dumped out the door on top of her brother who was already struggling to get back in.&nbsp;Before she was even all the way through the door, Gart pushed her back through with unpresidented force, but it was to late. Rosbesh’s eyes erupted with rage, but before he could let out the torrent, one word from Gart changed everything.</p><p>&nbsp;“Strangers.”&nbsp;He said with sincere authority, as well as complete desperation and panic.</p><p>&nbsp;Karish lept towards her daughter and wrapped her in her arms and carried her back to the bed before Gart had finished his one word report. Rosbesh clenched his stick and crept to the door in a crouch to peer out between the pelts.&nbsp;Dead ahead in the clearing stood a heavily dressed man at least 20 years old.&nbsp;Behind him in the woods was what seemed the shape of at least one other full grown man.&nbsp;It was clear they had seen that there was a virginal young female in the warm smoking hovel they had stumbled upon.&nbsp;Every ounce of blood flowing through their huge bodies now possessed a solitary focus.</p><p>&nbsp;There had been stories of people who risen slightly above a daily subsistence level existence.&nbsp;They had accumulated items of wealth and even beauty.&nbsp;Each time, however, at least so far, in other words for the last nine hundred thousand years, each time one man had managed to build something up over and above nomadic trinkets, stronger, younger, more aggressive men managed to attack, and tear it down.&nbsp;It was harsh, violent blood that survived in these frigid lands.&nbsp;To live past thirty was not to be expected.&nbsp;Chances to pass one’s seed on to the next generation was not an everyday opportunity.&nbsp;Most days were spent focusing on more elemental survival needs such as food and shelter.&nbsp;Even still, and for reasons not even clear to the participants being driven by those forces,&nbsp;the tremendously powerful will that this bare skinned species had to survive could not match the urge to practice the act of passing on one’s seed.&nbsp;Not even the horrendous forces nature unleashed upon these frozen crags of ice could in any way temper the chemicals that had been unleashed in these young men.</p><p>&nbsp;The two strange men came crashing through the door into the one room hut of old man Rosbesh.&nbsp;From the wall behind the door Rosbesh took his stick and shoved the thyroid gland in the first young man’s neck deep into his throat.&nbsp;Karish waited with a cooking pot in her had that glowed from the fire.&nbsp;The second man tried to block the swing to his face with his hands on which instantly raised awfull welts. Rosbesh took his stick and shoved it deep into the small of the man’s back deflecting him away from his wife.&nbsp;Then he smacked him in the ear with a biting whack.&nbsp;The two strangers rushed back from the house as quickly as they had come in.&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;There was no victory celebration in Rosbesh’s house.&nbsp;Dinner was eaten in cold, anxious silence.&nbsp;Outside the two angry marauders were licking their wounds and, as was the supreme forte of their race, planning a more cogent strategy than their first attempt, now that they had discovered that two young children don’t always live alone in a house deep in the woods.</p><p>&nbsp;Several hours later Rosbesh looked outside again.&nbsp;This time he could sense that there were now more than two strangers. Rosbesh knew he would loose.&nbsp;There was no civil justice in this world, no society, no community.&nbsp;There was no police force, and there was very little that lasted from one generation to another.&nbsp;There were no laws, except one; survival of the strongest.&nbsp;Karish looked at her husband with the look of complete blame only a wife can deliver.&nbsp;It was his stupidity pushing her babies out of her nest that had brought on this calamity. Rosbesh glared back at her attempting to defeat her young eyes which he had never had any problem doing so in the past.&nbsp;This time she held his stare effortlessly, the contempt in her eyes only growing. Rosbesh looked away.&nbsp;This was no time to confront a woman.</p><p>&nbsp;Women needed men but only if they could protect them.&nbsp;A pretty young woman would sometimes stay with two or three men.&nbsp;They would share her.&nbsp;This might afford her extra protection as well as require from her extra work.&nbsp;But such arrangements were unstable.&nbsp;Usually the men would kill each other off until only one was left with the woman.&nbsp;Brothers often might share a woman.&nbsp;But, brothers were also the most likely to try to kill each other to get sole possession of a wife.&nbsp;There was only safety in the family unit. Rosbesh had no brother and his two sisters were both taken by a man with a band of fighters who called himself Krugn.&nbsp;Both Rosbesh’s parents were killed in the process.</p><p>&nbsp;Rosbesh wandered the forest and somehow became a part of a loosely organized horde of young men who owed their association to that they were given fish and beer by a semi-merchant in a costal villiage.&nbsp;In return he was expected to a) not attack his village, and b) help protect him from harrasment from others, including Krugn.&nbsp;That was almost thirty years ago, many lives ago, many wives ago.</p><p>&nbsp;Rosbesh had met Karish, his current wife only a few years ago.&nbsp;&nbsp;He had long ago learned to hunt and trap and keep himself alive in his bitter land of ice.&nbsp;Success had led to an actual surplus, a long unfamiliar measure of wealth.&nbsp;This resulted in his taking to wandering into a fishing village on the coast where, so long as he shared his surplus skins and meat, there was a hall that served mead where he was welcome.&nbsp;It was here he learned about plans to loot and raid another settlement which had been discovered a few miles away. Rosbesh had no interest in the raid other than that he felt vaguely responsible for he seemed to remember that it was he who first revealed the existence of this settlement to mead drinking members of this community.&nbsp;In retrospect, a vicious raid could be the only expected result.&nbsp;knew of her village</p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="2d9db63e-86f4-4ae2-a781-b1bc2a467ce1" Title="The Scent of a Yong Girl" DateCreated="9/10/2018 1:58:48 PM" LastUpdated="9/10/2018 1:58:48 PM"><![CDATA[<p>now what's wrong with the cursor?</p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="5ebec98a-8070-43d2-af8c-7f18b4f241e6" Title="Down To the Long Hall" DateCreated="9/10/2018 2:01:12 PM" LastUpdated="9/10/2018 2:01:12 PM"><![CDATA[<p>nobody likes you except the pretty girl</p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="b7cde667-62a6-4d51-9a80-9f18d69a3caa" Title="" DateCreated="10/15/2018 9:03:51 PM" LastUpdated="10/15/2018 9:03:51 PM"><![CDATA[<p>Razor ice crystals crooked at jutting angles in a defensive scowl.&nbsp;A howling wind whipped about angrily in no particular direction.&nbsp;Low on the horizon, a dim star offered only a puny amount of light and little else.&nbsp;Spiny thornned brambles frozen stiff.&nbsp;The vicious, ground strangling vines would gladly shred the old man’s feet to ribbons.&nbsp;Reluctantly the miniature crystal structures gave way, shattering to shrapnel as Rosbesh crunched through the harsh bitter world into which he was born so long ago.&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;No morning that gave way to evenings where this man trudged across the gray ice marsh.&nbsp;No margin for error, no opportunity to make a mistake more than once.&nbsp;To fail to prepare for one winter ensured it was your last.&nbsp;To lie down for a moment’s rest was to die.&nbsp;To mistake the useless sun as a reference was to be tricked into traveling into a circle, something that did not happen twice in this unforgiving land.&nbsp;A few dozen hours without shelter or sustenance meant only one thing here: Death.</p><p>&nbsp;Although formidable, Rosbesh was not the biggest of men.&nbsp;However, he had managed to live a long time, which itself was something.&nbsp;At almost forty years of age, he had already lived twice as long as most.&nbsp;His young wife waited for him in the cold and only put some more peat on the fire when he arrived.&nbsp;No reason to attract undue attention from the smoke when he wasn’t there anyway.&nbsp;Their two children huddled dopily, wrapped in skins on the straw. Rosbesh burst through the well sealed and highly camoflogued door and struggled to quickly re-close it as the blustering wind strove to evacuate all the warmth that had been sealed in his tiny dirt hovel.&nbsp;Karish, the wife smiled at him. Rosbesh merely inhaled through his nose freeing a mass of thawed phlegm which he expelled in a loud grunt onto the packed mud wall.&nbsp;He glanced over at his listless children, an older girl and a boy of eight or nine seasons, both with white blonde hair and cobalt blue eyes.&nbsp;They wrapped their knees protectively near their chins, and stared at him wide eyed, anxious to see what meat his traps might have yielded, but ever uncertain of their father’s mood.&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;Seeing them napping there like vegetables doing nothing more than taking up space seemed to anger him.&nbsp;Never mind that is was minus twenty degrees outside, and the wind was howling furiously.&nbsp;“Kids these days!” Rosbesh thought.&nbsp;“All they do is sit around and wait to be fed. Why don’t they ever get out and do something?&nbsp;Why in my day…”&nbsp;Karish picked up the sack her husband had dropped and greedily uncover the duck he had recovered from one of his traps.&nbsp;She began to titter and hum and set about preparing a meal.&nbsp;The children took brief interest but showed no signs of making any effort to help their mother.&nbsp;At this Rosbesh snarled.&nbsp;“Unappreciative!”&nbsp;How he hated sensing his best efforts go unappreciated.&nbsp;He picked up his stick and started a loathing vent.&nbsp;Then he started roaring in such a way as to make it clear that he wanted the children to go outside.</p><p>&nbsp;Their mother was horrified.&nbsp;Any threat to the safety of her babies elicited her most primal response, but fear of Rosbesh and her and her children’s utter dependence on him for their existance, prevailed.&nbsp;Plus, the kids had been kind of getting on her nerves too.&nbsp;Before they could even get themselves well bundled, Rosbesh made it clear that it would be prudent for them both to make use of the front door immediately.&nbsp;Swan, his daughter, revealed as she was roused from the warmth of the straw bed, that she was rapidly taking on the shape of woman and was already being visited on by the curse. Rosbesh noted this with unconcealed disgust.&nbsp;“What a waste, a female child!”&nbsp;Her legs were long and her arms seemed just as long.&nbsp;Like a gangly spider she sprawled and stumbled about, having been in no way prepared to be flushed from her cozy nest.</p><p>&nbsp;Out she and her brother stumbled, her arms raised high as she attempted to slip through a fur coat like wrap.&nbsp;The awkward pose exposed the full riches of her body as she dumped out the door on top of her brother who was already struggling to get back in.&nbsp;Before she was even all the way through the door, Gart pushed her back through with unpresidented force, but it was to late. Rosbesh’s eyes erupted with rage, but before he could let out the torrent, one word from Gart changed everything.</p><p>&nbsp;“Strangers.”&nbsp;He said with sincere authority, as well as complete desperation and panic.</p><p>&nbsp;Karish lept towards her daughter and wrapped her in her arms and carried her back to the bed before Gart had finished his one word report. Rosbesh clenched his stick and crept to the door in a crouch to peer out between the pelts.&nbsp;Dead ahead in the clearing stood a heavily dressed man at least 20 years old.&nbsp;Behind him in the woods was what seemed the shape of at least one other full grown man.&nbsp;It was clear they had seen that there was a virginal young female in the warm smoking hovel they had stumbled upon.&nbsp;Every ounce of blood flowing through their huge bodies now possessed a solitary focus.</p><p>&nbsp;There had been stories of people who risen slightly above a daily subsistence level existence.&nbsp;They had accumulated items of wealth and even beauty.&nbsp;Each time, however, at least so far, in other words for the last nine hundred thousand years, each time one man had managed to build something up over and above nomadic trinkets, stronger, younger, more aggressive men managed to attack, and tear it down.&nbsp;It was harsh, violent blood that survived in these frigid lands.&nbsp;To live past thirty was not to be expected.&nbsp;Chances to pass one’s seed on to the next generation was not an everyday opportunity.&nbsp;Most days were spent focusing on more elemental survival needs such as food and shelter.&nbsp;Even still, and for reasons not even clear to the participants being driven by those forces,&nbsp;the tremendously powerful will that this bare skinned species had to survive could not match the urge to practice the act of passing on one’s seed.&nbsp;Not even the horrendous forces nature unleashed upon these frozen crags of ice could in any way temper the chemicals that had been unleashed in these young men.</p><p>&nbsp;The two strange men came crashing through the door into the one room hut of old man Rosbesh.&nbsp;From the wall behind the door Rosbesh took his stick and shoved the thyroid gland in the first young man’s neck deep into his throat.&nbsp;Karish waited with a cooking pot in her had that glowed from the fire.&nbsp;The second man tried to block the swing to his face with his hands on which instantly raised awfull welts. Rosbesh took his stick and shoved it deep into the small of the man’s back deflecting him away from his wife.&nbsp;Then he smacked him in the ear with a biting whack.&nbsp;The two strangers rushed back from the house as quickly as they had come in.&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;There was no victory celebration in Rosbesh’s house.&nbsp;Dinner was eaten in cold, anxious silence.&nbsp;Outside the two angry marauders were licking their wounds and, as was the supreme forte of their race, planning a more cogent strategy than their first attempt, now that they had discovered that two young children don’t always live alone in a house deep in the woods.</p><p>&nbsp;Several hours later Rosbesh looked outside again.&nbsp;This time he could sense that there were now more than two strangers. Rosbesh knew he would loose.&nbsp;There was no civil justice in this world, no society, no community.&nbsp;There was no police force, and there was very little that lasted from one generation to another.&nbsp;There were no laws, except one; survival of the strongest.&nbsp;Karish looked at her husband with the look of complete blame only a wife can deliver.&nbsp;It was his stupidity pushing her babies out of her nest that had brought on this calamity. Rosbesh glared back at her attempting to defeat her young eyes which he had never had any problem doing so in the past.&nbsp;This time she held his stare effortlessly, the contempt in her eyes only growing. Rosbesh looked away.&nbsp;This was no time to confront a woman.</p><p>&nbsp;Women needed men but only if they could protect them.&nbsp;A pretty young woman would sometimes stay with two or three men.&nbsp;They would share her.&nbsp;This might afford her extra protection as well as require from her extra work.&nbsp;But such arrangements were unstable.&nbsp;Usually the men would kill each other off until only one was left with the woman.&nbsp;Brothers often might share a woman.&nbsp;But, brothers were also the most likely to try to kill each other to get sole possession of a wife.&nbsp;There was only safety in the family unit. Rosbesh had no brother and his two sisters were both taken by a man with a band of fighters who called himself Krugn.&nbsp;Both Rosbesh’s parents were killed in the process.</p><p>&nbsp;Rosbesh wandered the forest and somehow became a part of a loosely organized horde of young men who owed their association to that they were given fish and beer by a semi-merchant in a costal villiage.&nbsp;In return he was expected to a) not attack his village, and b) help protect him from harrasment from others, including Krugn.&nbsp;That was almost thirty years ago, many lives ago, many wives ago.</p><p>&nbsp;Rosbesh had met Karish, his current wife only a few years ago.&nbsp;&nbsp;He had long ago learned to hunt and trap and keep himself alive in his bitter land of ice.&nbsp;Success had led to an actual surplus, a long unfamiliar measure of wealth.&nbsp;This resulted in his taking to wandering into a fishing village on the coast where, so long as he shared his surplus skins and meat, there was a hall that served mead where he was welcome.&nbsp;It was here he learned about plans to loot and raid another settlement which had been discovered a few miles away. Rosbesh had no interest in the raid other than that he felt vaguely responsible for he seemed to remember that it was he who first revealed the existence of this settlement to mead drinking members of this community.&nbsp;In retrospect, a vicious raid could be the only expected result.&nbsp;knew of her village</p>]]></Section>
  </Chapter>
  <Chapter Id="3ead5544-3de3-4341-85af-69ba108bf8bd" Title="Journey To The Future" Order="2">
    <Section Id="220ec15a-eb1e-4488-af07-cc59f1a7aacf" Title="The Phonecia Captian" DateCreated="9/10/2018 2:03:26 PM" LastUpdated="9/11/2018 5:38:05 PM"><![CDATA[<p>Imagine a dark ominous ship coming out of the mist.</p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="a5b7e524-f483-4bfb-abc7-e695fa0f6d98" Title="This Isn't Rome It's Just The Port" DateCreated="9/10/2018 2:05:25 PM" LastUpdated="9/10/2018 2:05:25 PM"><![CDATA[<p>What did I say before? Ivn had nothing to compare this to.</p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="a0cc49bc-8ee8-409f-a8ba-4ab5b84467bc" Title="The Lady's At Play" DateCreated="9/10/2018 2:06:33 PM" LastUpdated="9/10/2018 2:06:33 PM"><![CDATA[<p>left to their own devices they can't really blame it on the men.</p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="6144dc1b-3afe-4474-a664-19e83066cab4" Title="A Reluctant Gladiator" DateCreated="9/10/2018 2:08:15 PM" LastUpdated="9/10/2018 2:08:15 PM"><![CDATA[<p>Fernand the bull not really. He just didn't like the odds. and he wasn't feeling that good about himself.</p><p>I'm not going to dig my own grave. Just </p>]]></Section>
  </Chapter>
  <Chapter Id="d4b4b465-4552-490a-80ca-5248605728a5" Title="Ten Years A Galley Slave" Order="3">
    <Section Id="e8d57257-ebb6-49f1-b4af-6209fa6d1611" Title="Coming to Grips with Fate" DateCreated="9/10/2018 2:09:48 PM" LastUpdated="9/10/2018 2:09:48 PM"><![CDATA[<p>is this really my intended level?</p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="5fbf6e0a-68db-417c-b53d-52051a25407a" Title="Pulling Your Fair Share" DateCreated="9/11/2018 6:06:41 PM" LastUpdated="9/11/2018 6:06:41 PM"><![CDATA[<p>honor among thieves</p>]]></Section>
  </Chapter>
  <Chapter Id="aecf82a3-303f-45b6-bee9-183b39843656" Title="Alexandria" Order="5">
    <Section Id="a58c4873-2710-4768-af96-f3b6007aa910" Title="Letter of Passage" DateCreated="9/11/2018 10:13:22 AM" LastUpdated="9/11/2018 10:13:22 AM"><![CDATA[<p>Joe of A sends Ivn on a boat</p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="0efa5bb8-2f47-42fc-b307-d569e907a379" Title="The Opposite of Rome" DateCreated="9/11/2018 6:09:13 PM" LastUpdated="9/11/2018 8:46:29 PM"><![CDATA[<p>A gleaming white city close to the sun</p>]]><SubSection Id="522ad11f-3bed-4cff-ae4e-76dcae32d767" Title="Trade And Commerce" DateCreated="9/11/2018 6:10:18 PM" LastUpdated="9/12/2018 7:01:25 AM"><![CDATA[<p>The difference between Capitalism and Trade</p><p>The Phoenicians invented commerce. The Jews perfected, some would say corrupted it.</p>]]></SubSection><SubSection Id="258ad905-c4bc-4e33-b286-c78de1e495f7" Title="add a sub section here" DateCreated="9/11/2018 8:40:48 PM" LastUpdated="9/11/2018 8:40:48 PM"><![CDATA[<p>Joe of A sends Ivn on a boat</p>]]></SubSection></Section>
    <Section Id="06e30c39-58af-4a76-bb16-82ed9e566a8c" Title="The Brucheum" DateCreated="9/11/2018 8:48:58 PM" LastUpdated="9/11/2018 8:48:58 PM"><![CDATA[<p>how to describe the opulence of a Cleopatra set … dwell on the details  </p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="a9d73006-7545-4121-bab1-cd4bfdc2f415" Title="Chests of Gold" DateCreated="9/12/2018 6:56:16 AM" LastUpdated="9/12/2018 6:56:16 AM"><![CDATA[<p>An idea is hatched</p>]]></Section>
  </Chapter>
  <Chapter Id="6c8a8d95-a53b-4672-b839-1e0927159939" Title="the Angel of Galilee" Order="6">
    <Section Id="49d9c7a2-5907-424e-a757-86046d721549" Title="Joseph the Cuckold" DateCreated="9/11/2018 5:09:46 PM" LastUpdated="9/11/2018 5:09:46 PM"><![CDATA[]]><SubSection Id="8c040d32-18ad-4c07-98f3-f1ee25f4a03b" Title="A Mother's Love" DateCreated="9/11/2018 5:09:57 PM" LastUpdated="9/11/2018 5:09:57 PM"><![CDATA[<p>the editor focus.</p><p>This is another story I once fleshed out. Now I have to rebuild it. So Close.</p>]]></SubSection><SubSection Id="9cfa9135-dc99-46b0-98ec-690cfc156eeb" Title="Marriage problems" DateCreated="9/11/2018 5:13:17 PM" LastUpdated="9/11/2018 5:13:17 PM"><![CDATA[]]></SubSection></Section>
    <Section Id="273892f5-70a9-44f0-8d0d-ba9bd978b13c" Title="The Sons of Joseph " DateCreated="9/12/2018 6:19:54 AM" LastUpdated="9/12/2018 6:19:54 AM"><![CDATA[<p>the editor focus.</p><p>This is another story I once fleshed out. Now I have to rebuild it. So Close.</p>]]></Section>
  </Chapter>
</Book>