<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Journal>
  <Entry Title="Maybe God is telling me to stop wasting my time on this" DateCreated="4/3/2014" Id="076c9feb-175a-4a96-acc1-cb5062b4a9e3"><![CDATA[Believe it or not I really may be getting somewhere on this.  There I was working on get a job, and sorta got that working.  Then just for the hell of it, while I was cleaning up some errant links on my lovely home page I got it in my head to create a web journal
And in one day here it is.  This thing leverages all I was able to figure out with xml as in Lodge Secretary and even the knockout I just learned while building GetaJob.  Life is funny that way.  If I knew when I took that interview on Monday what I know now after getting up to speed on knockout I would have done a lot better and might well have gotten it.
  If I had built something like this thirty years ago it might be a little more impressive.  They didn't have the tools I have now.  it would have been a lot more complicated. So what do I do now?  I'm sitting out here on my lovely back porch looking at the purple lilac popping out.  I'm listening to the Ed Show on my outdoor TV.  I just want to go back in my office and work more on one of the last things ]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="Some people just can't work for other people" DateCreated="4/3/2014" Id="0d054640-30eb-4b41-9507-b8d9603ecd73"><![CDATA[Once there was a way to get back home.  
   
    What if I were to go down and visit Kingsville, go down to see Nick Harrel?

Most people don't have to worry about getting fired all the time.  Few people have lived a life like mine.
My life is a little different>  That's a good thing.  It's not a good thing on many levels, especially 
financially and socially, personally and professionally.

This is a time for me to finally accept who I am and be good with it.

I'm sitting here on my new touchscreen laptop with backlit keys sitting in my living room watching a movie on NetFlix on my
big screen TV with my wife sitting on her bigger all in one wireless monitor with a built in computer
and my friend Mark is here looking up something on my Acer tablet; the Android Transformer.

And I'm writing into the web log journal that I built and pushed up to this my website.

We're watching the movie "Jobs" about Steve and Apple.  He, of course is the same age of me, as is Bill Gates for that matter.

Steve Jobs had his success, lost his company, and had his comeback and of course he has been dead for several years.
Bill Gates has long ago retired.  
It is really time for me to realize and accept what is and has become my life.
Here I have this little web log editor.  
Even Steve Jobs has known the experience of getting fired.
When Jobs got fired who was in the better position?  The company and those people who think they are better off without a
good talented person. Jobs did ok.  Looks like he even got his family beck.
And I am going to do ok.  
No one has ever asked me to come back.  No one has ever given me credit for much of anything
No one has really very much appreciated me.  There's no taste, no style, design.

  Now I am watching the scene with Steve Jobs meets Ives the designer guy.   
He is known for creativity, style and design.  I need to exercise my creativity.




what are the chances this will work the first time?

Actually, it worked surprisingly well.  I'm really getting the hang of this.
I almost feel a little happy.
Now on to other things.

wait. It's working even better than I thought

]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="Forever 29" DateCreated="4/3/2014" Id="fa13fcfb-0552-4427-9527-899f013aabc0"><![CDATA[
What's long and hard that women get on their wedding night when they marry Polish men?  A new last name.  
Har Har Har

I too am exactly twenty-nine this year.  ..(times two).  So you have been somewhere on this earth for half my life now.

Actually, we will share this distinction again next year.  A few weeks after you turn 30 I will be sixty.
Let me tell you something about a man my age:  I am not going to change.  It's too late.  I am what I am.
I am a fat, bald, vaguely Jewish looking old man.  I had a hernia operation on my big belly last week.  I am walking around with a cane.
I would do anything to get you back in my life and to get back in your life, but it's unlikely I am going to change into what ever you want me to be anytime soon.  What do you want me do?

It looks like I'm retired.  I was supposed to have a phone screen interview today, but, it's been slow going this time.  I can't even see myself getting offered another contract.  When I amble in it's not what they're looking for any more.  It seems God is telling me its time to give up, kick back and try something else.  Maybe it's time to write my book.

I have been working steadily for over thirty-five years, but I have never been able to hold the same job for more than a year so I have never gotten anywhere.  Your mother was right to divorce me for "insufficient means of support".  It's amazing I lasted in the job market as long as I did.  A person has to squint and hold their head in a certain way to feel good about oneself when they have a track record such as mine.  Sometimes I share your disdain and disgust towards me myself.  Maybe I'm just not that good at what I do (except I am).  More likely my charming personality is just not that well suited to work in the corporate world for other people.  Sometimes I feel good about myself but, mostly I wish I could have changed what I was and what I am.  Unfortunately, I just don't see that happening. Still it's a shame you have decided to dismiss me the way you have.  I know you must feel great anger and disappointment towards me.  Well, I really have no clear idea what it is.  Parents cause emotional issues for all of us.  Still, I am certainly a rather "interesting" person and it's a shame you seem not interested in getting to know me.

It's now been almost ten years since I have even seen you.  I can barely remember the incident.  Something to do with me embarrassing you in front of a rent-a-cop down in Deep Elum.  I apologize.  I miss you.  I think about you every day.  I wonder what you are like, what your opinions are on things, what your passions are, what you find funny, what matters to you.

You will always have my complete unquestioning love.  I love you and Alexander more than anything. But you have to help me understand what you are like as a person.  I do not want to be your friend necessarily, although that would be nice.  I want to be your father.

I am your father.  The Bible commands that you respect me.  You have blocked me from calling you.  If you ever want to, it is up to you to finally break this and contact me.  Tell your husband that if he is to be a man he should travel to meet me and ask for my blessing.  I will give it to him. 

I am still very proud of you.  As a rebellious daughter you could have done other things to hurt me.  I have not seen your image on any porno web site, despite my extensive research, and there are thousands of girls out there, all with complex daddy issues I'm sure.  You have no neck tattoos that I know of.  You seem to have career ambitions.  You married the man you dated for ten years (Thank God).  You are absurdly beautiful.  You can thank me for those incredible blue eyes.  I may have hurt you, but you certainly have hurt me very much too if that has been your intention.  You have made my life meaningless and empty.

Please God don't keep me away from my grandchildren if they ever come.  That would be evil.

Please call me someday.







]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="going in for hernia surgery. Time to quit smoking" DateCreated="4/3/2014" Id="b7781965-f32e-42e2-948e-9333f56fae15"><![CDATA[I just got off the phone with a doctor, a surgeon who is going to perform a hernia operation on me.
So the time has come.  Here I am going in for operations.  The end is really getting near.
As for my job prospects, things have never looked worse.

]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="Things left to do" DateCreated="4/3/2014" Id="78b3a11f-8493-4476-940c-7660a8b91a06"><![CDATA[clean up the garage
looks like I will never get anything finished.  I have wasted another year. What an empty hole.
Is there still any chance?  

The Partisan Divide
   One way to look at it is racism.  More than racism it's ethnic tribalism.  All sorts of 'isms. Here in the US perhaps we don't see the same thing happening all around the world all the time.  

Financially there's no hope for me ever to retire, or so it seems.  On the other hand, I'll probably be able to get a programming job.  On the other hand, all my life I have been threatening to throw it all in and write my novel which I know will be a success and will make my name.  It is what I must do.  It is what I have always been meant to do.


   If the republicans win the Senate in November, and they probably will win, they will raise taxes.
I listened to three or four of the Sunday morning talk shows. There was the requisite amount of griping hatred of Obama, criticism of Obama policy, criticism of everything Obama does, blaming Obama for everything from ebola to the VA.  But Lindsey Graham, after implying that Bush had won the war in Iraq and Obama deliberately turned it over to terrorists, was asked what he would want to see happen if republicans take control of the Senate.  He actually said that the republicans need to compromise on revenue.  He complained about sequestration for his beloved military, but he actually also mentioned that the budget for the CDC, the Center for Disease Control had been cut and the Secret Service budget has been cut.
  Republicans think they can flip the Senate and surely will win in 99% of incumbent congressional seats by criticizing Obama.  Fox News did a piece on how the government can't handle things the way they would like.  In the same breath they bay for less government and less regulation except when it comes to regulating for profit abortion clinics.  Their magic word remains Obamacare: that which has destroyed the economy and robbed America of its freedom.  If this black man had insurance who wandered into the emergency room of an expensive Dallas hospital, ten miles from Parkland where the poor are supposed to go had insurance he would have been checked in for an untrimmed toenail.  Hospitals remain for profit institutions, not government regulated quarantine screening agencies as it seems the republicans now suddenly seem to expect.
   Alright, enough of my complaints about republican hypocrisy.  Nothing new there.  Back to my point.  They will raise taxes.  Not on the rich.  Not cut loopholes for well lobbied interests like oil or wall street.  So how will they fund this new revenge war?  
   If congress were in session they would probably be spending their time debating a new travel ban on all African countries.  






give it a header and a shortcut Icon-  done

still have Flitter and my books 
and a proper nested to do list (flitter)

but for now time to get up


next task: start writing one of my books.
]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="Dear Jim, I'm sorry I yelled at you the last time we talked. " DateCreated="4/3/2014" Id="8ef016d5-8410-433a-a420-e3af00a0031e"><![CDATA[I'm sorry I yelled at you the last time we talked. 

I had listened to hate radio earlier that day and wanted to vent. I know those right wing talkers are just prurient pornographers providing entertainment the market rewards, feeding the susceptible what they want to hear, but still, within the first amendment there still should be some accommodation for truth in advertising.  What got me all worked up was talk about the debt and the deficit (constantly confusing the two) and coming to the conclusion that we Just Need to Cut Spending.  This, supposedly, is the essence of the Tea Party message.  Who ever heard of a corporation seeking to curtail investment and growth?  Sure, when priorities or market conditions change redirecting always occurs, but as an ongoing strategy, long term never includes cutting spending as a goal.  Unless, of course, if you hate the very idea of government.

What a coincidence that you only hear this kind of Ruby Ridge, Nevada rancher posse kind of talk when the party they hate is in office?  How can you not see a fundamental need for and a value for government?  It is what defines us as a communal organism.  We have come down from the trees to live in huts.  Humans are now social animals.  That's just the way we are.  When people work together they can bring down larger game.  They can perform specialized tasks so than one man can work the fields and another can cobble shoes.  And all this requires a system of laws.  We do better when we work together and so, despite Ronald Reagan's disingenuous quip, government is good.  Sure, waste fraud and abuse will always be with us.  To say you believe in government and a well ordered fair and just society does not mean you condone waste fraud and abuse.  (except to an idiot)  Less government they scream, (except when it has to do with female reproductive choices).

Now you have, on a daily basis, anticipation, almost a longing for total collapse.  The republican party now actively roots for failure.  Deep down hate drenched republican conservative religious fanatics hope and pray things will only get worse. It is all based upon their central gripping teeth clenching snarling contempt for Obama.  You would rather see the economy crumble and millions of people suffer just so it might reflect badly on Obama.  Better to somehow make Obama look bad than do anything that might in any way benefit the country as a whole.  

Your much hoped for end of the world is centered on not global climate change, not military adventurism or nuclear proliferation, you have pinned all your fantasies for the demise of Obama on The Deficit.  It's the deficit they yell.  The world is coming to an end and total collapse is imminent because of the deficit. And so, of course, they conclude; We have to cut taxes and cut spending (except, of course on military weapons).

I love it especially when the hate radio talkers couch their biggest lies in explicit proclamations that what they are about to say is indeed the real truth, and what the biased left wing liberal media doesn't want to know.  It's like when an advertiser proclaims its product is bigger or crunchier than the competition or their previous model.  First that tells you that size or crunchiness are issues, and second that they are feel the need to address that specific deficiency.  Fox and hate radio talkers have learned well the propaganda techniques of the big lie that if you repeat the lie enough times how well it obviates the truth.  Then they take a central premise which is a lie, and build on it and embellish it so that the essential underlying lie becomes assumed.

Concerning imminent total collapse, actually history indicates the doomsayers probably eventually will be correct.  Nothing lasts forever and no civilization has managed to last all that long.  The deficit, or more specifically the debt will never go down.  It depends on whether you consider the Federal Reserve a part of the government or a private entity, a rich banker who can personally profit from the indiscriminate printing of money.  When they buy however many hundreds of millions in commercial bonds every month that money from my understanding comes from essentially nowhere.  They just print it.  

My exasperation if not anger I was feeling when you last called me is because of why the current administration feels necessary to resort to such questionable  fiscal policy instead of more legitimate financial policy.  Because the Congress fears that if they do anything to help the economy it might somehow indirectly shine a good light on Obama and they would rather see the economy fail, they would rather see people suffer.  This is no exaggeration.  If you think I am wrong on this point ... well you are so blinded by ideology I am sure you do not think this is the reason why republicans are loathe to doing anything.  Public works, infrastructure, anything, certainly anything resembling public assistance republicans hate.  Why?  Well this is one of the central defining differences between the parties and how a person defines the word "fairness".  Liberals define fairness more in terms of social justice.  Conservatives define fairness as: I got mine, the rest of you can go to hell".  Government is bad.  Rugged individualism.  Fairness means I got mine and I deserve to keep it, all of it.  Social justice and social responsibility are evils designed to diminish the individual.

Not only does my definition of the word fairness have more to do with social justice than gun rights, I think that for the ideologically pure republican system to work they have to view the world as a level playing field.  I do not see the world as an ideal inherently fair level playing field.  Some people are born less beautiful and healthy and smart than others.  That's just the way it is.  And everybody who doesn't have the good sense to die young eventually gets old.  Even Paul Ryan will someday not be able to dunk the basketball the way he could in his twenties. 

As for taxes.  I made a lot of money last year and I am right at the sweet spot of taxpayers, a working man with few ways to hide my earnings and few ways to declare extravagant deductions.  I pay the highest rate and the highest percentage of my income.  Rich people may pay an absolute greater amount, but I doubt it is ever a bigger total percentage than me.  But I think the rich should pay more in taxes for another reason: the distribution of wealth.  The world is not level or fair and wealth does not distribute itself fairly or rationally.  You may think that a newly hired CEO can lay off five hundred people and make others do twice the work so he can give himself an extra fifty million dollars because he deserves it.  I suspect CEOs do it not because he is so much better and so much more deserves it, but just because he can.  You may believe that you deserve to earn ten thousand times more because you work ten thousands times harder than a coal miner or someone who spends eight hours a day standing in front of a chicken fryer, but I feel at best you may only be a few dozen times more deserving.  The only way I see to effect the naturally unfair distribution of wealth is the tax code.  A survey of history will reveal that the Middle Class does not come into existence and does not remain existent without deliberate intent and constant vigilance.  That is why I am retiring.  Working for a living is just not worth it.  Working hard is for fools.  The system is stacked against the working man.

by the way, I am now retired.

I got let go from another contract two months ago.  This time is different.  I do not see myself taking another job unless it is a perfect opportunity and it just falls in my lap.  I give up.  After thirty years it's time I realized that I can't work for other people.  I don't fit well into the corporate environment.  It's amazing I lasted as long as I did.  Rugged individualism for someone like me may be a little more complicated.  Ironic that republican self-reliance may work better for conformists who fit in and thrive in the corporate environment.  

So I am retired.  I have some money and I have a wife who works.  Soon I will cash in my meager retirement account and hope that it takes me up until Social Security.  I am going to finally write one of those books I've been meaning to write all my life.  I've put in my time.  I've been earning a paycheck for thirty four years.

I am going to continue writing computer programs, but I am going to do it for myself.  Given that others have been willing to pay me to create apps for them means there must be some value in what I do.  Maybe I can write an app myself and market it somehow.  For the past two months I have been working on a project that automates the management of a Masonic Lodge.  You can look at it here.  I don't think there is anything else like it out there.  It uses all the most modern development practices used in the programs I have worked on for some of the world's largest corporations.  But, instead of building things for others the way they want them built now I can design and build things the way I want.

I am going in for a hernia operation tomorrow.  

I am going in for a hernia operation tomorrow.  The days of invincibility have officially passed.  Now I am the patient sitting in the waiting room with all the other old fat people.  I took a CT scan the other day for the first time in my life.  Please say a pray for me to your favorite deity.  If I make it through next time you see me I will have a big scar on my currently pristine belly.  I'll be shuffling and wheezing like the old man I am.]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="Yet another setback" DateCreated="4/4/2014" Id="0c88d0e1-c014-44ba-8f0f-9a56016b8b66"><![CDATA[Suddenly I'll get an unauthorized permissions error.  Here I spent all this time just in order to get past the permission issues.  Wasn't it working just a while ago.  

Even so, I have gotten a little further.
 I have built this little blog site.  I need to add some log in capabilities.  No problem 
and I would like to put in some improved page sizing functionality
I want to build my first jquery widget, a resize tool.



]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="Lodge Secretary is ready" DateCreated="4/23/2014" Id="2b09c498-ad55-43bb-be9d-8d79020f5c85"><![CDATA[My name is Curtis Rhodes.  For over twenty years I have worked as a computer database application developer. LodgeSecretary.net makes use of the latest technologies and most advanced design techniques found in projects developed for some of the worlds largest corporations and many of the best practices I have acquired over the years.  And I am offering it free of charge to all Masonic lodges.  (If after a year you are still using it and find it useful, a voluntary annual donation would be appreciated).
   In addition to maintaining a address and status information on lodge members, LodgeSecretary.net does much more.  For one thing it keeps track of dues.  It also keeps track of officers and committees, allows you to enter minutes, and has an events calendar.  LodgeSecretary.net is designed around the individual member.  One of its main features is the Masonic History Report which gives you a detailed chronology of each member.  In addition to all the chairs he has held and committees he was on it can track Masonic awards and titles, military service, job history, and any other accomplishment you might want to mention.  You can add publications, pubic office or anything else.  This way when a brother passes to great beyond you will have something to say about him at his eulogy and his record will remain.
   LodgeSecretary.net also allows you to add wives and children and parents going all the way back to Noah.  This way we can keep track of widows, which is one of our charges as Masons.  
   I started this project over a year ago but it has been largely rewritten for one specific reason: security.  Each lodge that choses to use this system has its own separate stand alone password protected database file created.  No lodge data is co-mingled and while I suppose the NSA could get in and look at your data if they tried, no one who is not a member of your lodge can access your data accidentally.
  If you get a chance, please take a look at what I have done.  There is still a bit more to be done and I could use some encouragement.  If you have any questions or comments or require technical assistance please contact me at curtishrhodes@hotmail.com 
]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="Five Inducements" DateCreated="4/28/2014" Id="89fc89e5-42f5-412e-8ac2-2023b51459f2"><![CDATA[In June I am going into the East as they say in Masonry, which means I will become the leader of my lodge.  Here is the draft of a speech I am thinking about delivering.



What induced you to become a Master Mason?  That is a question we are sometimes asked.  I am going to offer a little talk here mentioning five things that might seem worthy motivations.  Knowledge, or wisdom. What could be controversial about knowledge?  Citizenship, tolerance, public education and, finally justice.  These all seem perfectly lovely and noble and perfectly innocuous ambitions.  Knowledge, citizenship, tolerance, education and justice.  Yet I may not make it through this talk because it turns out each one these noble ideals will turn out to be more and more inflammatory.

1. Knowledge
Masonry encourages us to pursue knowledge.  The light it is sometimes called.  It seems pretty straightforward, but imagine living in a time when the pursuit of knowledge is a controversial or even dangerous thing.  History, sadly is not a straight line of continuous progress.  There may be a brief period when a province may break off the from the Papal states and you have Michelangelo and Leonardo and a flowering of art and knowledge.  But then those who might feel threatened come in and burn the secular in bonfires of the Vanities and you have a thousand years of dark ages.  Then you might have a king who breaks away because he wants a divorce and for a brief period of time you have Shakespeare and Newton and Francis Bacon,  But soon the puritans come back and push knowledge back down.  It is during these times when somewhat secretive organizations become necessary to protect and preserve the accumulated wisdom of the world and pass it down until such time as the light is allowed once again to shine.  This I consider to be an important if not central piece of Freemasonry.  We are currently living through one of the greatest explosions of technology and expansive flowerings of knowledge the world has ever known.  Yet, here in Texas especially, we can see the stirrings of those might feel threatened by science and knowledge and would seek to push it back when it doesn't nicely conform to their views.  I am here to forever stand in opposition to these people.  
   Back in the day there was no formal science such as molecular biology or electronics or particle physics or organic chemistry or engineering.  Science referred to an organized deductive way of categorizing information.  Geometry stood as a metaphor and a synonym for for all of science and knowledge and even wisdom Sophia.  The word knowledge with a silent k is germanic English word.  In Greek the word is guu-no-sis pronounced no-sis with a silent G.  There are some who might speculate that the letter G stands for Geometry.  It might just as well stand for knowledge or gnosis.  Anyway, that's not too controversial.  I am in favor of knowledge and think it's a good thing and am will to join with those who will defend it.

2. Citizenship
We are taught as Mason to cheerfully comply with the government of the nation in which we live.  What does this mean?  Does it mean that we should comply with the government only when the elected leader is someone who professes our personal preferences?  What if we are living under a regime that is violating the first principle I just mentioned and is burning books and endeavoring to suppress knowledge?  Our founding fathers many of whom were Masons, including those who conducted the Boston Tea Party, participated in a revolution against the government.  So what does it mean to be a good citizen?  I believe that it is important for a Mason to appreciate the importance of a well ordered society, which is another word for government, in and of itself.  Ours is an organization consisting of structure and rules.  I think it's important to note that George Washington and the Masons that founded our nation were not against government per-se.  They sought to improve the system of government in the United States. It is one thing to to be opposed to waste, corruption and abuse.  It is quite another thing to say you are against the very idea of government itself.
   Is it enough to pay lip service to patriotic sounding platitudes, and anything of anything having to do with the military but feel comfortable chanting "less government, "limited government" and anti-regulation code words, such as States rights?  If you feel that way, why would you be a Mason?  As a Mason you may not allow yourself to be seduced by the fears that society might accidentally provide charity assistance to people you have been told not to consider worthy.  Some people who have benefited from society will feel the urge to pull the ladder up behind them.  But Masonry is not based on the premise: "I've got mine and I will be damned if I will share any of it with any one else."  Masonry actually is quite the opposite.  Ours is a charitable organization.
   Once upon a time there was a slick talking Hollywood cowboy, a GE corporate pitch man who ended up making the most important philosophical statement of the twentieth century.  The most significant philosophical statement of the post war era.  There was once some Greek guy who made a comment about shadows on a cave wall.  Descartes once said that thinking proves existence; I think therefore I am.  Jeremy Bentham once said something about utilitarianism, Thomas Jefferson represents a long line of thinkers that had some things to say about unalienable human rights.  There was Machiavelli, Thomas Hobbs, Spinoza, Voltaire, and Rousseau, so to say a man is responsible the most important statement and influential philosophical impact on the thought process of all of you is, well, sort of impressive.  A few years earlier president Kennedy used a Chiasmus; a rhetorical device where the words of the first sentence are rearranged in the second sentence. The coward of Bagdad who left 238 Marines behind, a traitor who funded death squads in Nicaragua by selling our nations most technologically advanced surface to air missiles to our enemies and by shipping cocaine on military transports into our inner cities, the only divorced person to hold his office who destroyed the middle class by slashing the taxes on the top 1% while raising taxes on all rest, meaning that 90% percent of Americans have not had a raise for thirty years since the traitorous the coward made his sarcastic probably disingenuous quip which has become the most important philosophical statement in any of our lifetimes.  The smart ass quip mocking JFK was, of course: "Government is not the solution, Government is the problem."
    Today it is popular, especially in the still embittered South, to agree with the wealthy propagandists determined to remove any trace of regulation,  and agree that everything government does is bad and incompetent and corrupt and private enterprise will always run things better.  I have worked in private corporations all my life and have seen plenty of corruption and incompetence.  Corporations once they reach a certain size become indistinguishable from the public sector except that they are strict hierarchies completely controlled from above with no recourse for the employee with the lesser job title.  I am tired of this anti government talk and consider it antithetical to Masonry.

3. Tolerance
Another thing Masonry stipulates is that a man must believe in a higher power in order to be a Mason but that it does not matter which faith tradition a man favors.  The germanic guttural sound Got from which is derived the English word God, is not a Hebrew or Aramaic word or even a Greek or Latin word.  Some scholars differentiate the books of the Old Testament by whether they use the word Jehovah or Elohim or Adoni which is often translated as Lord which is another word for king.  The Gospels in the New Testament mostly use the word Father, or Father in Heaven.  Anyway it could be argued that the English word God does not actually appear in the Bible.  The people of the Old Testament have a concept of a deity so far beyond we three dimensional sequential time bound humans' capacity to even begin to pretend to understand what we are talking about that it is inappropriate for us to even attempt to utter the name or the word and are certainly never allowed to write it down.  And there are many faith traditions that we know of many thousands of years older than the two thousand year old one that may be prevalent here in Texas.  Osiris and Isis begat the savior Horus seven thousand years earlier. Chrisha was nailed to a tree in the Hindu Vedas three thousand years before that.  Mithurs and Dynoyses, or Odin or oeastra or Buddha or Shinto or Tia Chee or Allah, or even pre Isrealatic deities of the trans Jordan the phoenician or Philistine Assyrian Hiram Abif.  For some of us it is possible to accept an all encompassing faith built from all the wisdom of the past.  For some it is very important to believe that their particular faith tradition is the one true path and everyone else must be wrong.  Masonry has been interpreted to allow this so long as you pay lip service to a professed tolerance of others even though you think them to be wrong.  This is necessary because frankly 99.9% percent of Masons here in Texas adhere to a belief system that demands it... That you consider all who don't adhere to the one true faith to be eternally misguided.  All I can say is that this is fine.  Who would not want to possess such complete certainty?  My only question is, but why then are you Masons?

4. Public Education.
This is sort of like my first reason for being a Mason, the pursuit of knowledge, but different.  I did not say just education but public education.  I did not learn this until I became a Texas Mason but it turns out Masons essentially invented public education.  The earliest lodges in Texas were often two story buildings.  On the second floor there would be the lodge but on the first floor they would hire a one room school teacher to take in all the children of the town folk and the nearby farms.  It seems funny that an organization supposedly intent on preserving its secrets would be so interested in disseminating the light of knowledge to others, but, really, that is what Masonry is all about.  We are to take in the young initiate, the apprentice and train him up into the light.  An educated citizenry is essential for a well functioning democratic system and a strong growing vibrant nation.  And yet public education is today under attack more than it has ever been.  First there are those who wish to impose their ideological agenda on parts of the academic curriculum they consider a threat to their personal beliefs.  And now there are the profit seekers who see the great investment our nation has made in public education as place to siphon off tidy profits.  Public education is under attack and no place more than here in Texas and again even though I didn't appreciate this that much before I became a Mason I see it as our charge as Masons and perhaps our most important task at the current time to fight and do whatever it takes to defend public education.

5. Justice.
Finally, there is one last thing that induced me to become a Master Mason.  Even though I already talked about religion and even dared sully the sainted reputation of the man who made the snarky remark about government being the problem not the solution, this is certainly going to be the most outrage inducing thing I will say today.  I shutter to point this out to all of you, but other than intangible well being the only way a person who has worked through the ranks and become a master of his trade can benefit from it is if he is able to leverage all he has patiently struggled to master in the market place.  One other thing that the coward of Baghdad death squad funder who sold stinger missiles to our enemy did that contributed to the destruction of the middle class as much as his tax cuts for the rich was what he did to the air traffic controller trade guild.  I will not say the U word out loud because all of you in this room have been so thoroughly trained by the only news outlet you watch to so hate organized labor.  But it might not surprise you to learn that I happen to think that justice for the working man is only possible if he is allowed to somehow to stand up for himself and demand a fair share at the table.  What is the final reason that induced me to become a Master Mason? So that I might travel to different lands and earn Master's wages.  


-- 
Curtis Rhodes]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="Another month lost.  Passed by with nothing to show for it." DateCreated="5/16/2014" Id="2eeaac95-499f-469f-b21b-b4d4dec9fcda"><![CDATA[I cry out for help.  Look at me I am an old man wasting my life away with nothing to show for it.  So let me count my blessings.
At least I have another contract starting up.  Another decent paying job.  I will not be making as much as I was at the last two places I worked.  2013 will probably stand as the high water mark of my life.  That's a weird thought.

If I could do anything right now what would it be?  Maril is running off to do some errands.  Time for me to go look at porn, rub myself and smoke.  Yes, you're quite right; I could be making better use of my time.
Thank god I have another contract that starts Monday. Since my hernia operation I have been sitting around, mopping around, demonstrating just how little one can get accomplished even if they have all the time in the world.  I wonder what this new job will be like?  I wonder if I will even be able to last there my typical three to four months.

Let's face it:  I have never been able to last anywhere for much longer than three months.  How is it that I even made it low these thirty five years?
Let me count.  I am sitting out here on my lovely little back porch on a beautiful sunny spring day tapping out a journal entry.  I am too old to put together enough of a coherent string of thoughts to create a proper book of any kind.  All the greatest works of literary art are created by people in their early twenties.  My time has long passed.

Garker an unlikely rare good friend just sent me an email sputtering so absurd, so far out there conspiratorial it makes me realize how off the wall the things I excrete out onto the web must seem to others.  Disjointed, angry, confusing, an amalgam of hate drenched Obama birtherism theories.  What purpose does it serve; to make him feel better about himself somehow?

 
Tomorrow I start a new job, always an exciting and hope filled time.  Hope may not be the right word.  I don't expect much in the way of success.  For the past thirty years I have quite conclusively proven to myself as much as to anyone else that I will get fired within my normal three to four months.  Oh well.  

I'm sitting here outside on my patio, the weather is lovely.  I'm listening to the cavalcade of Sunday political talk shows as I tap on my laptop.  I just wonder how long my across the alley way neighbor can spend mowing his tiny back yard?  Last night I banged out an actual page of my twenty year old novel.

60 Minutes Syndrome
Now it's another Sunday night.  It looks like I have thoroughly squandered a record four month stint of unemployment.  Feb Mar Apr and May.  
Another year has melted away.  Shorter of breath and closer to a meaningless empty death.
Even if I completed my book who would care?  What would it matter?
 ]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="my defense" DateCreated="8/29/2014" Id="a4e39405-269d-4091-bf0d-8f5eca09b430"><![CDATA[Briefly put; let me assure you that I have no intention of voluntarily expelling myself from Masonry.
I look forward to hearing the charges presented against me, and having the opportunity to defend myself.

As I understand it, I am charged with two things: 1. building a web site that had naked and pornographic pictures, and 2. posting a journal entry on my web site that was found objectionable.  

I wish to address the journal posting first.  It so happens that I am proud of what I wrote and would be delighted to defend each of the points that I made.  The article delineates my understanding of Masonry and explains why I chose to be a Mason. The journal article presents five explicit points. If you condemn me, it becomes your obligation to present evidence against each of these propositions.

The first item mentioned on my list of what Masonry means to me is Knowledge.  While to me it seems unnecessary and absurd to have to defend the pursuit of knowledge, I tired to explain that throughout history brief periods of enlightenment are often followed my long dark ages.  There are those who, in their desire to preserve the status quo, prefer to suppress knowledge with ridicule and sarcasm if not torture and burning at the stake.  And, it is my theory that in times when knowledge was under threat that some felt it necessary to meet in tyled seclusion away from cowands and ease droppers in order to preserve and protect ancient wisdom until the tides of prevailing prejudice subsided and the light was allowed once again to shine.  Forgive me, but I can't help but sometimes feel the victim of just such ignorance.  

  Before I continue, let me boil this indictment down to what I see it to be.  The word conservative is defined as one who desires to maintain the status quo, one who longs for the good old days of their childhood when things were ideal. Many Texans, the vast majority, proudly describe themselves as conservative.  I find this astounding.  To me, that is like saying; I am set in my ways, unwilling to accept, let alone embrace change, and am resistant to new ideas.  Currently, as we all know, the political divide in this country has become fractious, approaching violent.  Civil friendly debate has become impossible.  I, obviously, am an unrepentant liberal, and that is the real reason these charges have been brought against me.  Each of the five points I list as why I became a mason reveal an increasingly liberal position and therefore increasingly annoying and inflammatory to conservatives.    
Conservatives hate the insinuation that they are opposed to knowledge because it implies they are stupid, which is not the same thing and certainly not the case.  Is it smart for me to defend my position, or even present it when I know that the key to getting along is to go along?  I know that is impossible to ever change a grown man's political opinion.  Still, that the light of knowledge is a positive thing is a part of masonry I can't wait to see you argue against.

  Having stated that I suspect it is because I am a liberal that these charges are being brought against me, an important point is that I am not being accused of making these comments within the lodge.  I am being accused of future crimes.  The complaint is that I might if I were installed as Master of the Lodge, stand in the east and preach these liberal ideas.  The case is not that ever did such a thing but the fear that I might.

The second tenant of Masonry I managed to turn into a liberal cudgel I called Citizenship.  Conservatives love to rail against government (except when it comes to the military).  All this talk will go away if a politician wins who wants to expand government to include a warden in every precinct who will investigate every woman's miscarriage.  Now there's a subject that should never be discussed anywhere least of all a Masonic lodge.  If I ever were to say something like that inside a lodge that would be more substantial grounds than what we have here.

The third reason I gave as to why I joined the Masons is perhaps the most infuriating, and perhaps not coincidentally the most important to me. I wrote that the very act of conceding the most basic, primary and fundamental tenant of Masonry is to admit that Jesus and God are two different things.  After all, if you say that a man need only to express belief in a higher power, the textual literal material factual implication is that a man can believe in God and still not be convinced in the divinity of Jesus.  For Christians Jesus is God.  Through an elaborate tripartite construction Christians insist that Jesus is not a god or of god, but the God.  Furthermore, according to proper Christian dogma any one who is not saved and accepting of Jesus is not merely wrong, but condemned to hell.  
  Secretly, most Christians privately admit to themselves that Jesus was probably a man, of god, but not necessarily God.  After all, what does it mean to be God?: that you can shoot lighting bolts out of your finger tips?  And how can Jesus die and be brought back to life if the whole time he was God? And if he did not actually die for our sins because he was God the whole time, then what's the point of the whole thing?  Anyway, there are some of us with very well developed spiritual beliefs who have a little trouble with the precise divinity of Jesus.  And this is what attracted me most to Masonry.  So it begs the question; how can you be a Mason and accept that others are capable of believing in a different form of God, and still hold to required believe that you can only come to God through Jesus?  Well, obviously, that is a question that must not be asked.  In my opinion, that is why I am being banished from Masonry: because I dared to ask that question, in Farmers Branch Texas.

Then I added another controversial annoyance.  It turns out that Masons essentially invented the concept of public education.  Those who oppose knowledge and oppose government tend to despise the very notion of the public part of public education.  They want to privatize it and have a problem with it being secular.  The Grand Lodge has a charter that essentially mandates that it spend most of its endowment on public education, but, this being Texas, most Masons would rather do anything but.  

Finally, I offered an idea that those who will only watch Fox News might find the most egregious, perhaps even more than my observation that Masonry demands that one entertain the idea that Jesus and God are two different things.  I suggested that Masonry is modeled after an institution that conservative republicans loath more than even public education; a labor union.  Now, I happen to believe that world is not a level playing field.  The planet Jupiter has a greater gravitational field than a little asteroid.  Is it fair that a larger mass can attract more dust and space debris than a million smaller ones and thus continually grow bigger at the expense of its smaller neighbors?  Perhaps it's not fair, but I believe that physics is physics and that's just the way it is.  So it is with financial capital or wealth.  Labor unions are wonderful and a good thing and important to society and necessary to preserve the middle class in a world that is what it is although perhaps not a completely fair level playing field.  I support unions and think there should be more of them and can't help but notice that Masonry comes out of that very tradition.

Having said all this, despite the reasons why I joined Masonry and what I think Masonry should be, I accept now that the dying remnant of Masonry in north Texas has become a pathetic wastrel of anything I had hoped for.  I gave a lot of time and effort to my lodge.  I tried to make friends and contribute.  I made my way through the chairs and was days away from becoming master of my lodge when these charges were filed.  I have not been back since and it turns out I don't miss it all.  Not one person in the lodge has reached out to me or even made the slightest gesture of friendship or brotherhood.  

As to the other charge; that I had a link to another web site that I developed on my home page, I admit it freely.  I make no apology.  There is not law against putting a site on the web that shows naked pictures.  Such web sites are actually quite common.  They make up a very large percentage of world wide web.  I doubt I am the only Mason that ever visited one.  I look forward to seeing exactly what you accuse of in this regard.  As far as the accusation that I supplied a link from the lodge web site to my personal home page; that is not true.  One would have to observe the link to the Lodge Secretary application that I wrote and know how to manually backspace to get to my home page and then root around to find the ogglebooble web site, as well as get to my journal.  By the way, I work as a professional application developer.  I have or have had many links.  One thing that I worked a long time on was a very sophisticated membership database for managing a lodge.  It has a functionality for tracking dues, committee assignments, an events calendar, inventory, a cash book, attendance, chairs, pictures, and personal information about members.  That is what I had a link to from the lodge web site. It still needs some work, but I haven't touched it since the charges were filed.

-- 
Curtis Rhodes

]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="the Hemlock cup" DateCreated="8/31/2014" Id="987414cf-c846-4554-ab19-7504e4d18715"><![CDATA[
Briefly put; let me assure you that I have no intention of voluntarily expelling myself from Masonry.
    
 It's been six almost months already since I the charges were filed.  After all the time and effort I attempted to put into the lodge it's surprising how little I miss it, and clearly how little my brothers, my supposed friends have missed me.  The world we live in seems especially torn apart with ethnic and sectarian strife.  If you look back in history perhaps it's always been that way.  Through it all people try to find friendship and a sense of belonging by seeking out like minded folks.  That was my intention when I joined Masonry.  Unfortunately, it didn't work out.  
   Let me first explain what I had hoped to find in Masonry.  I didn't know much about Masonry before joining except wild rumors from Dan Brown novels.  But, the first thing that Masonry says about itself publicly is the part about how, while you must profess a belief in a higher power, a creator god, it is not necessary to profess a faith in any particular religion.  This appealed to me greatly because I describes my personal theology well.  As it turned out, few other Masons at least in my lodge seemed to appreciate or understand what it really means to say that it's ok for people to believe in different formulations of The Great Architect of the Universe.  What it means is that Jesus and God are two different things.
   A study of the history of Christianity reveals that this subject has been hotly contested topic for a very long time, since the very beginning actually.  First there was the split between Paul and the balance of the actual Galilean apostles led by James brother of Jesus.  That controversy had to do with whether simply professing your faith was enough or if your acts mattered.  By acts James meant following the law, specifically the Jewish sacraments including circumcision.  Although any reading of the words of Jesus clearly indicate which camp he would have been in, the mysticism of Paul quickly won out.  But, the next big split had to do with the divinity of Jesus.  The Vandals who ultimately sacked Rome in the fifth century were followers of Arian who made the obvious argument that the son followed the father who alone was eternal.  However, the promise of full body resurrection into heaven regardless of your sins or your adherence to any laws proved immensely popular and coincidently extremely lucrative to increasingly powerful bishops and priests as well as innumerable evangelical preachers.  
   They had a conference in Nicaea and put it to a vote.  The theology came down to two Greek words, Homoiousianism or Homoeanism, "of God", or "like God".  Just saying Jesus was like God wasn't good enough.  It didn't make him special enough.  It made him too much like the rest of us.  We all are like God, born in his image and all that.  The vote was close but Arias lost.  The powerful bishops felt they had a stake in making Jesus as God-like as possible.  But they didn't want to be pantheistic.  There could only be one God.  So they came up with an elaborate formulation called the Trinity.  The word trinity appears zero times in the bible and to this day no one knows what it really means, but since that time professes belief in what they call the tri-partite God.  
   It's unclear how many of even the most devout fanatical Christians actually believe that the Son and the Father are both equally uncreated and forever eternal and if Jesus is a deity, I mean the deity how could he have suffered pain on the cross and died as be risen again if he was a god the whole time, I mean the God, and if Jesus didn't suffer on the cross what's the point of the whole thing.  Clearly most Christians for the past two thousand years have managed to work through these blasphemous questions without any problems except for a few annoying people like me when I was a twelve year old in Sunday school.  Actually, I was fine in my Christian faith except that there was a globe in that Sunday school class.  I had never seen one before and I would look at it a lot.  I remember I once told my teacher that it looked like Africa and South America could fit together and that Spain could fit nicely in the Gulf of Mexico.  The teacher who had already tired of me assured me it was the stupidest thing she had ever heard, but then she told me that the people who lived over in India believed in different gods than we do and people in China believed in another different religion.  Most little kids might just say, "Oh that's weird" which was how she seemed to feel about it, but for me it struck me hard as one of the most astounding things I had ever heard.
   The idea that other people believed in different gods besides Jesus really upset my world.  Jesus was one God lots of other people, perhaps a majority of the other people on this same small Earth the John Glen had just rocketed up and around believed in entirely different religions.  I did not become an atheist.  I didn't not doubt that there is more to this world than all of us put together can know for certain.  I just started to put Jesus in perspective and continued my search across a much bigger playing field with a lot more questions.  I have continued on in that search all these years through quantum physics and multi-dimensional space time.  I take solos in knowing that all we can learn is nothing compared to what is really going on, but that there's bound to be a reason why we're here and perhaps even a purpose.  
    Following the Council of Nicaea a rival bishop in Alexandria where Arias also was from, Athanasius, out of all the stories that were circulating about Jesus, picked four, along with collected works of Paul and declared them the only permissible texts.  He chose Matthew, Mark, Luke and John because those were the only ones that allowed for the interpretation that Jesus was actually a divine being.  The rest, which contained much the same teachings of Jesus and more took for granted that Jesus was a great teacher but that he was a mortal man.  
   I have nothing against Jesus who I think was a fine fellow.  The best proof that he was at least based on an actual historical figure is that many of the things written about him are troubling and confusing and not entirely perfect behavior.  Politically he was a liberal socialist bordering on anarchist.  Socially he was cynical and argumentative, had problems with his mother, and would probably not be welcome in many of the classier congregations that profess to worship Him.  The part about Him being a deity I find a little troubling, and when preachers insist on the having to be born again part and that there is no way to the father except through the son I can't help but see how demeaning and insulting and antagonistic that is to the balance of the world population.  


 



   




I look forward to hearing the charges presented against me, and having the opportunity to defend myself.

Conservative ignorant dogma is the orthodoxy of fools.  The current spasm of racially tinged, hate drenched fanaticism may eventually abate, the fever may break, if not here in Texas even though the essential dynamic may persist the epoch.  The idealized view of Masonry in the journal entry for which I am being dammed started with the 


As I understand it, I am charged with two things: 1. building a web site that had naked and pornographic pictures, and 2. posting a journal entry on my web site that was found objectionable.  

I wish to address the journal posting first.  It so happens that I am proud of what I wrote and would be delighted to defend each of the points that I made.  The article delineates my understanding of Masonry and explains why I chose to be a Mason. The journal article presents five explicit points. If you condemn me, it becomes your obligation to present evidence against each of these propositions.

The first item mentioned on my list of what Masonry means to me is Knowledge.  While to me it seems unnecessary and absurd to have to defend the pursuit of knowledge, I tired to explain that throughout history brief periods of enlightenment are often followed my long dark ages.  There are those who, in their desire to preserve the status quo, prefer to suppress knowledge with ridicule and sarcasm if not torture and burning at the stake.  And, it is my theory that in times when knowledge was under threat that some felt it necessary to meet in tyled seclusion away from cowands and ease droppers in order to preserve and protect ancient wisdom until the tides of prevailing prejudice subsided and the light was allowed once again to shine.  Forgive me, but I can't help but sometimes feel the victim of just such ignorance.  

  Before I continue, let me boil this indictment down to what I see it to be.  The word conservative is defined as one who desires to maintain the status quo, one who longs for the good old days of their childhood when things were ideal. Many Texans, the vast majority, proudly describe themselves as conservative.  I find this astounding.  To me, that is like saying; I am set in my ways, unwilling to accept, let alone embrace change, and am resistant to new ideas.  Currently, as we all know, the political divide in this country has become fractious, approaching violent.  Civil friendly debate has become impossible.  I, obviously, am an unrepentant liberal, and that is the real reason these charges have been brought against me.  Each of the five points I list as why I became a mason reveal an increasingly liberal position and therefore increasingly annoying and inflammatory to conservatives.    
Conservatives hate the insinuation that they are opposed to knowledge because it implies they are stupid, which is not the same thing and certainly not the case.  Is it smart for me to defend my position, or even present it when I know that the key to getting along is to go along?  I know that is impossible to ever change a grown man's political opinion.  Still, that the light of knowledge is a positive thing is a part of masonry I can't wait to see you argue against.

  Having stated that I suspect it is because I am a liberal that these charges are being brought against me, an important point is that I am not being accused of making these comments within the lodge.  I am being accused of future crimes.  The complaint is that I might if I were installed as Master of the Lodge, stand in the east and preach these liberal ideas.  The case is not that ever did such a thing but the fear that I might.

The second tenant of Masonry I managed to turn into a liberal cudgel I called Citizenship.  Conservatives love to rail against government (except when it comes to the military).  All this talk will go away if a politician wins who wants to expand government to include a warden in every precinct who will investigate every woman's miscarriage.  Now there's a subject that should never be discussed anywhere least of all a Masonic lodge.  If I ever were to say something like that inside a lodge that would be more substantial grounds than what we have here.

The third reason I gave as to why I joined the Masons is perhaps the most infuriating, and perhaps not coincidentally the most important to me. I wrote that the very act of conceding the most basic, primary and fundamental tenant of Masonry is to admit that Jesus and God are two different things.  After all, if you say that a man need only to express belief in a higher power, the textual literal material factual implication is that a man can believe in God and still not be convinced in the divinity of Jesus.  For Christians Jesus is God.  Through an elaborate tripartite construction Christians insist that Jesus is not a god or of god, but the God.  Furthermore, according to proper Christian dogma any one who is not saved and accepting of Jesus is not merely wrong, but condemned to hell.  
  Secretly, most Christians privately admit to themselves that Jesus was probably a man, of god, but not necessarily God.  After all, what does it mean to be God?: that you can shoot lighting bolts out of your finger tips?  And how can Jesus die and be brought back to life if the whole time he was God? And if he did not actually die for our sins because he was God the whole time, then what's the point of the whole thing?  Anyway, there are some of us with very well developed spiritual beliefs who have a little trouble with the precise divinity of Jesus.  And this is what attracted me most to Masonry.  So it begs the question; how can you be a Mason and accept that others are capable of believing in a different form of God, and still hold to required believe that you can only come to God through Jesus?  Well, obviously, that is a question that must not be asked.  In my opinion, that is why I am being banished from Masonry: because I dared to ask that question, in Farmers Branch Texas.

Then I added another controversial annoyance.  It turns out that Masons essentially invented the concept of public education.  Those who oppose knowledge and oppose government tend to despise the very notion of the public part of public education.  They want to privatize it and have a problem with it being secular.  The Grand Lodge has a charter that essentially mandates that it spend most of its endowment on public education, but, this being Texas, most Masons would rather do anything but.  

Finally, I offered an idea that those who will only watch Fox News might find the most egregious, perhaps even more than my observation that Masonry demands that one entertain the idea that Jesus and God are two different things.  I suggested that Masonry is modeled after an institution that conservative republicans loath more than even public education; a labor union.  Now, I happen to believe that world is not a level playing field.  The planet Jupiter has a greater gravitational field than a little asteroid.  Is it fair that a larger mass can attract more dust and space debris than a million smaller ones and thus continually grow bigger at the expense of its smaller neighbors?  Perhaps it's not fair, but I believe that physics is physics and that's just the way it is.  So it is with financial capital or wealth.  Labor unions are wonderful and a good thing and important to society and necessary to preserve the middle class in a world that is what it is although perhaps not a completely fair level playing field.  I support unions and think there should be more of them and can't help but notice that Masonry comes out of that very tradition.

Having said all this, despite the reasons why I joined Masonry and what I think Masonry should be, I accept now that the dying remnant of Masonry in north Texas has become a pathetic wastrel of anything I had hoped for.  I gave a lot of time and effort to my lodge.  I tried to make friends and contribute.  I made my way through the chairs and was days away from becoming master of my lodge when these charges were filed.  I have not been back since and it turns out I don't miss it all.  Not one person in the lodge has reached out to me or even made the slightest gesture of friendship or brotherhood.  

As to the other charge; that I had a link to another web site that I developed on my home page, I admit it freely.  I make no apology.  There is not law against putting a site on the web that shows naked pictures.  Such web sites are actually quite common.  They make up a very large percentage of world wide web.  I doubt I am the only Mason that ever visited one.  I look forward to seeing exactly what you accuse of in this regard.  As far as the accusation that I supplied a link from the lodge web site to my personal home page; that is not true.  One would have to observe the link to the Lodge Secretary application that I wrote and know how to manually backspace to get to my home page and then root around to find the ogglebooble web site, as well as get to my journal.  By the way, I work as a professional application developer.  I have or have had many links.  One thing that I worked a long time on was a very sophisticated membership database for managing a lodge.  It has a functionality for tracking dues, committee assignments, an events calendar, inventory, a cash book, attendance, chairs, pictures, and personal information about members.  That is what I had a link to from the lodge web site. It still needs some work, but I haven't touched it since the charges were filed.

-- 
Curtis Rhodes

]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="oops a brief breeze passed" DateCreated="8/31/2014" Id="7fa939d5-204b-4e37-8d16-b6a1e6d421c2"><![CDATA[What what is all this that a certain company wants to know?


+floors&rls=com.microsoft:en-US:IE-Address&tbm=isch&imgil=5O8QPPjpnbeQjM%253A%253B8wMUpjelJJ31nM%253Bhttp%25253A%25252F%25252Ffishandpeaches.blogspot.com%25252F2012%25252F01%25252Fcosmati-floors.html&source=iu&fir=5O8QPPjpnbeQjM%253A%252C8wMUpjelJJ31nM%252C_&usg=__RYU5fY4HEj7oN3IiaeNdnmq3x1Y%3D&sa=X&ei=Ko8DVPSGJ87LggT3soLgBQ&ved=0CDUQ9QEwAw&biw=1093&bih=514#facrc=_&imgdii=_&imgrc=5O8QPPjpnbeQjM%253A%3B8wMUpjelJJ31nM%3Bhttp%253A%252F%252F4.bp.blogspot.com%252F-4gsJvGm5zw8%252FTxbaZ8WQO_I%252FAAAAAAAABtg%252Fe5GHetz7xl8%252Fs1600%252FSM%252Bin%252BTrastevere%252BCard%252Bcosmati.jpg%3Bhttp%253A%252F%252Ffishandpeaches.blogspot.com%252F2012%252F01%252Fcosmati-floors.html%3B1600%3B1106]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="Thought I'd something more to say" DateCreated="5/18/2015" Id="f11ebc70-d577-460a-9b5f-ccfa2a1fb9a4"><![CDATA[So now I have a new walkie an for the pool.
  If I come down here all I ask is that you don't use the words Jesus and God interchangeably.
  Bikers in Waco.  Ramadi back in the hands of the Sunnis we call ISIS.  No one left in my life except Marilena. 
My boss sent me a text.  Now we have a report.  That's something to feel good about.
Now I can relax for a while.  Summer has begun.






  ]]></Entry>
  <Entry Title="I don't remember writing this app" DateCreated="7/20/2018" Id="d7b63035-09e7-41dd-b00f-ee9e063bdaeb"><![CDATA[So I'm look at the code in my GoDaddy PLESK account control panel. How the hell did I do this thing in the first place?  
It's an .asmx web service. Wow.
All I want to do is get something up and running that I can publish, update and maintain. 
I want it to be a .dot net core app. 
Well, on the other hand, I have all the hooks up there already.
]]></Entry>
  <Entry Id="d844b20a-99af-4b01-ad00-0f56aac43531" Title="things to do hhh" DateCreated="8/9/2018"><![CDATA[add a cancel button  - done
add status message - done

still trying to publish api 

Finally I got a restful api working and its nice. 
Now to Add IMAG


just put back the put verb

what's going on now?

what was I trying to do. I still needed this blog -- Even Though I will now create a databased blog.]]></Entry>
  <Entry Id="15553fd6-3e00-4dd1-8f0d-3edd4d8dcaf4" Title="funny how time slips away" DateCreated="8/22/2018"><![CDATA[now I seem to have this working ]]></Entry>
  <Entry Id="142eb678-4a63-489b-a23d-ace8c7d2eae9" Title="Now the Post" DateCreated="8/22/2018"><![CDATA[this has been working

Looks like it worked this time]]></Entry>
  <Entry Id="98a73bf6-5f20-4f24-90e6-5dada248fbe1" Title="" DateCreated="8/26/2018"><![CDATA[]]></Entry>
</Journal>