<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Book>
  <Chapter Id="a2a3aac5-b00a-4e13-a832-848cdbc90e47" Title="From 640k to TeraBytes" Order="01">
    <Section Id="ebb3f9fb-6525-44a1-a2a2-4bb4a8d74ec8" Title="" DateCreated="9/17/2018 9:21:42 AM" LastUpdated="9/17/2018 9:44:59 AM"><![CDATA[<p>Remember floppy disks? In the early days of computer programming we counted how many bytes we used to store things because it was easy to run out of storage and memory. The Y2k panic was based on the fear that many bank transactions and such were stored with a two digit year and the flip from 1999 to 2000 would cause all sorts of systems to start misbehaving. Ever hear of thing called file handles? Original eight byte machines could only keep so many references to things like linked libraries of code or data tables. To open up one thing you'd have to drop something else. </p><p><br></p><p>This book tries to tell the story of where we are now in the year {2019} and how we got here. A few years ago Walmart was the nation's and thus perhaps the world's largest company, beating out even the oil producers such as Exxon and the auto manufactures such as GM. Walmart doesn't manufacture any thing. What Walmart provided is something call Supply Chain Automation. By tracking the sales of products using bar code scanners and RFID tags they were able to optimize retail delivery and provide low prices thorough high volume. Supply Chain automation is one of the computer programs we will discuss. </p><p><br></p><p>Currently the largest companies in the world are on-line platforms themselves. We have come a long way in the past few years and this author has been right there through much of it. Not all the innovations computer programming were completely wonderful. Complicated algorithms in the mortgage business led to a world wide financial crisis. A lot of jobs have been lost. File clerks and things like billing departments no longer exist. Eventually there may be no jobs left that can't be replaced by ATM's or other types of robots.</p><p><br></p><p>Computers are not smart. Computers are electronic machines that can perform essentially three functions. They can iterate or step through a series of instructions, they can loop back and repeat a series of steps repeatedly until some condition is met, or they can branch which is to jump to one set of instructions or another based on a condition. That is all that computer processors can do at the lowest level; iterate, loop, or branch. This doesn't get too technical but as you can see, we do talk about things like file handles and machine level operations. </p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="d2600151-a0d3-463c-89f9-8ee7f61746a0" Title="From Two Lane Country Roads To Eight Lane Highways" DateCreated="9/17/2018 10:27:19 AM" LastUpdated="9/17/2018 12:15:54 PM"><![CDATA[<p>  Did you ever see a ribbon cable? If you ever opened an older PC there were these flat wide cables which were a really a row of wires stuck together into what looked like a fat piece of duct tape. The word serial means that each piece of information come one after the other. To make things faster a ribbon cable can send eight, or sixteen, or thirty two, or now sixty four pieces of information in parallel. Ribbon cables were normally attached to input/output devices. Keyboards are input devices. A monitor or a speaker are output devices. An I/0 device provides both input and output. A hard drive is an I/O device; it can both accept input and provide output. Garbage in, garbage out. </p><p> A memory device typically stores information in bytes which consist of typically eight bits. Bits can be set to either one or zero, on or off, yes or no, a binary choice, Eight bits together can store 2 to the eighth power or 256 possible combinations. But, to find the value of a given byte in memory it has to have an address. You need the address of a byte, it's location on the disk, in order to learn it's value. There are different addressing strategies. You can set a base address and an offset to be more efficient, but a machine can only make use of so many locations in memory based on the number of the address locations it can handle. When we are talking about an sixteen or thirty two or sixty for bit machine were are talking about how many addresses in memory it can deal with both internally and on dick, which in turn greatly determines how fast it can operate. Ribbon cables determine how many bits can be processed at one time. Like lanes on a highway, more traffic can move faster based on how many wires are in your ribbon. Now they have more normal looking wires with lots (64) tiny optical fibers. </p><p>Likewise the processing chip can process 64 bits at a time, making it orders of magnitude faster. But that's seldom the bottleneck. Physical operations like reading memory from a disk happen in real time; tenths or hundredths of a second, while processors can operate at nanosecond speed. That's why there's two types of memory.    </p><p><br></p>]]><SubSection Id="ecb382ca-8b52-4c3d-916a-a3fddf85e685" Title="The Bottleneck" DateCreated="9/17/2018 10:52:39 AM" LastUpdated="9/17/2018 12:00:22 PM"><![CDATA[<p>Memory doesn't have to be on round spinning disks any more. Now there are flash drives and the like, but they're not the same as RAM, random access memory: If I ask you your mother's maiden name you can probably access it from the random access memory in your brain almost immediately. But if I ask you for Abraham Lincoln's mother's maiden name you may have to go to some page of some book on some shelf in some section of the library and look it up. That takes much longer. Of course now you'd just Google it, but it would still take a little longer. </p><p><br></p><p>  When you go shopping for a new laptop they advertise how much memory it can store on its <span style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); background-color: transparent;">internal hard drive or s</span>olid state memory chip, which can be up to a terabyte or more. They also tell you how much RAM memory it has; typically four or eight or even sixteen kilobytes. In terms or how fast your computer will run RAM is the most important number. Even if the app you're running is a web browser where the speed or your connection is usually the bottle neck but still the amount of RAM you have still matters because even web pages can pull down a lot of stuff that takes up memory. No matter how fast your chip the slowest part of any operation, the bottleneck, is the fastest the operation will take.  As we will see, in computer programming this consideration is true all over the place.</p><p><br></p><p> If you run out of ram paging happens. Paging is when the ram slides a bunch of stuff onto the hard drive and replaces it with other more recent stuff. Then when you perhaps alt-tab to another window, maybe a local app like a painting tool or a game, or even when you move to another major part of your program. paging may have to slide one page into ram and another one out. A traditional hard drive has an <span style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0); background-color: transparent;">aperture head&nbsp;like the needle arm of a phonographic record player only with a laser eye. </span>Any operation that involves moving a physical component happens in real space-time and can never be faster than the speed of electrons stored in ram. It's like having to look up Lincoln's mother's maiden in a library book.</p><p><br></p><p><br></p><p><br></p>]]></SubSection><SubSection Id="1120fee1-64e3-4bc4-9411-8bd033d899ef" Title="Can Nine Women Have a Baby In One Month" DateCreated="9/17/2018 12:21:48 PM" LastUpdated="9/17/2018 12:21:48 PM"><![CDATA[<p>Speed of performance on the hardware level involves mastering mechanical issues Optimizing the performance of software is an aspect of consideration for the software developer. But, the art and science of writing a computer program involves more than that. It is a creative process.</p>]]></SubSection></Section>
  </Chapter>
  <Chapter Id="3f9a3227-d55d-4b1e-a933-b5f75e7ef70c" Title="The development Life Cycle" Order="">
    <Section Id="340db07e-b333-4675-b00b-0c63349f7741" Title="" DateCreated="9/17/2018 12:10:20 PM" LastUpdated="9/17/2018 12:10:20 PM"><![CDATA[<p>The title of this book is a commentary on the well respected maxim that a little planning is a good thing.</p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="44df70ef-ef4c-4aca-990d-805f927c4f60" Title="Whole thoughts" DateCreated="9/17/2018 12:12:11 PM" LastUpdated="9/17/2018 12:12:11 PM"><![CDATA[<p>  When an idea comes to you it doesn't come in pieces. It doesn't come in discrete sequential steps.</p>]]></Section>
    <Section Id="a6419849-a1d0-4772-ae20-fbf813ebfbaf" Title="Team Player" DateCreated="9/17/2018 12:14:38 PM" LastUpdated="9/17/2018 12:14:38 PM"><![CDATA[<p>  Software development has turned into a corporate operation with lots of people playing different roles. But, I'm here to argue that developing a program is like writing a book or a song</p>]]></Section>
  </Chapter>
</Book>